medbullets.com 2013-10-08

# Privacy Policy - Medbullets.com

###  Purpose and Summary 

To inform visitors and members of Orthobullets.com (a product of Lineage Medical, LLC) of how their private information will be gathered and how it will be used. This policy only applies to Orthobullets.com and other websites created by Lineage Medical, LLC. If we provide a link that leads to the website of another organization, this privacy policy does not apply. 

Orthobullets.com is meant to be a private community for orthopaedic surgeons. Therefore, it is our highest priority to protect the privacy of members so they feel secure to participate on Orthobullets.com. At any time if a physician feels uncomfortable with our privacy policy, the physician may request that we remove all of their personal information from our database. 

###  Visitor Personal information collected how we use it. 

When you view pages and graphics on our Web sites, the following information may be recorded in a log file: 

  * The time and date of your request
  * The Internet address of your computer
  * The browser and operating system you are using
  * The page that you are viewing

We use the information noted above to facilitate effective operation of OrthoBullets.com and Lineage Medical, LLC Web sites and to measure overall anonymous usage by users. We do not review use of individual users unless a user's account is associated with 1) attempts to violate the security of OrthoBullets.com and Lineage Medical, LLC computer networks, 2) activity that degrades the performance of OrthoBullets.com and Lineage Medical, LLC Web sites, 3) activity that may be related to copyright violation, or 4) if we are required to disclose this information by law. 

###  Member Personal information collected how we use it. 

Lineage Medical, LLC maintains a visitor database based on registration information. Lineage Medical, LLC has no intention of sharing this information with other organizations for marketing purposes. If, for the purpose of creating revenue in order to keep this site available for free we decide to change this policy, we will contact all members in advance and will not provide any information without the explicit permission of the members. The success of Lineage Medical, LLC and Orthobullets.com as a free educational site depends on the feedback from registered members. Therefore, it is the highest priority of Lineage Medical, LLC to protect and respect the privacy of physician members so that physicians feel their information is secure. At any time if a physician feels uncomfortable with our privacy policy, the physician may request that we remove all of their personal information from our database. 

###  How we use your email 

From time to time, Lineage Medical, LLC may send you e-mails regarding items of interest to you, including updates on OrthBullets.com and responses to questions you have posted. 

###  Security and E-Commerce 

Lineage Medical currently has no E-Commerce functions. 

###  Cookies 

Some Lineage Medical, LLC Web sites, including OrthoBullets.com, send visitors a cookie (small computer file) that, in most cases, contains a unique serial number. Each time our Web server receives a request for a page, it checks to see if the cookie is present - this enables us to determine how much of our traffic is from repeat visitors. 

Additional cookies may be sent by Lineage Medical, LLC Web servers to facilitate interaction between your Web browser and Lineage Medical, LLC web servers. Please note, however, that some services will not work if your browser does not accept cookies. 

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 

###  Disclosure required by law or emergency circumstances 

Personal information is information that can be used to identify or contact you. Lineage Medical, LLC may release personal information to third parties: 1) to comply with valid legal requirements such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena, or court order; or 2) in special cases, such as a physical threat to you or others. In the event that we are legally compelled to disclose your personal information to a third party, we will notify you unless doing so would violate the law or court order. 

###  Disclosure in the context of mergers and acquisitions 

In the event of a merger or acquisition of Lineage Medical, LLC, your personal information will be protected and not release to the "acquiring" organization without your explicit permission. As stated above, it is the highest priority of Lineage Medical, LLC to protect and respect the privacy of physician members so that physician feel their information is secure. 

###  Disclosure to Lineage Medical, LLC operations and maintenance contractors 

OrthoBullets.com and Lineage Medical, LLC operations and maintenance contractors who may have limited access to your personal information in the course of providing products or services to Lineage Medical, LLC. Access to your personal information by these contractors is limited to the information reasonably necessary in order for the contractor to perform its limited function for Lineage Medical, LLC. We also contractually require that our operations and maintenance contractors 1) protect the privacy of your personal information, and 2) not use or disclose your personal information for any purpose other than providing us with products and services. 

###  Conclusion 

These statements convey the current privacy policy of Lineage Medical, LLC, parent company of OrthoBullets.com. Lineage Medical, LLC reserves the right to alter this policy, but is responsible to contact all members in advance and give them the option of removing any personal information from our database.
